Hello guys welcome to another video of stock
market friends, the
September quarter results have been out from ICIC Insurance, the
unaudited results have been out, the second
quarter and the half year ended which is the
audited financial result, along with this, the
interim dividend of equity share at ₹ 0.5 has also been
declared, the record date is
fixed for 23rd October, so we will go to the
results, if we talk about the numbers, the
numbers have been given in lakhs this time, if
seen, the gross premium return if
seen, this time is 7 lakh 59000
759 crores, last time 852 crores, last time the
premium
return was 6948 crores, it is down in quarter year, it has
increased year on year, the net
return premium is 5313 crores and
premium earned was 5651 crores,
after which the total income was 6582.7
crores, in the last quarter 6683 crores,
in the last year the total
income is 5850 crores.  It has increased quarter on quarter year on year.
Expense was Rs 5830 crore
last quarter and Rs 5429
crore last quarter. Total
expense was Rs 5186 crore.  There is an increase quarter on quarter.  It
also increased year on year.
Whereas income also increased year on year.
Now the expenses have also been
increased here.  But after that the
operating profit of the company is around Rs 752 crore.
Last quarter was worth Rs 654 crore.  Last
year the operating profit was Rs 664 crore.
Increased quarter on quarter year on year.  But despite that, the company's
net profit came out to be Rs 89.5 crore.
747 crores in the last quarter.  Last
year the profit was Rs 694 crore.  It has been seen
increasing quarter on quarter year on year.
And if we
talk about this, the NPA of Guys Company is
₹16.3 last volume of EPS is ₹14.9 last
EPS is ₹1.9.  It has increased quarter on quarter
year on year.  But now
here we talk guys about some
ratios etc.  The solvency ratio is around 2.7%
which has increased quarter on quarter year
order and here the net
retention ratio which is the intention ratio of
75.3% is also seen to be very better.
Apart from this, if you look at NPA here, then if you
look at unrealized and without it, then the
yield on investment that is seen is 2.2%
and
if we look at it with unrealized value of 0.4%, then the overall
result has been presented very well, if we look at it,
very strong results are being seen,
good results were seen from the company, if we
talk about the share, it closed at ₹1865, there is a
profit of 1.7%, there is a loss of 2.11% in five days.  There
is a loss of 1.8% in 1 month.  Now let us
compare Guys with its Earn
Estimate.  So the company's revenue
estimate was Rs 6182 crore.  Generated Rs
6582 crore which is seen as the same.  The
profit estimate was Rs
773 crore.  The company generated no out
break.  Beaten by Rs 89.5 crore.
Overall, very strong results have been presented.
So see you in the next video.
Till then, bye-bye.